Benjamin Vølund

Software Engineer

n benjaminvoelund.dev

/bvoelund

i̇̃⋒ /bvoelund



ABOUT ME

My name is Benjamin Vølund and I'm 27 years old. I'm a experienced Software Engineer, and have worked primarily with development of frontend applications over the last couple of years. I'm a "dad-to-be" and currently situated in Silkeborg, Denmark. In my sparetime I enjoy basically anything nerdy, from gaming to building with Lego bricks.

EDUCATION

Engineer in Softwaretechnologies

Aarhus Universitet, 2018 - nu

→ Bachelor degree as a Software Engineer at Aarhus University

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer @ Jysk

Aug. 2021 - Present

→ Been part of developing multiple frontend systems - primarily a modern cash register system for the company stores, using React.

Internship @ Kamstrup

Feb. 2020 - Jun. 2020

→ Internship as part of my education. Got to work on my own project from the ground up, in the shape of a WPF Application in C#.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

TypeScript, JavaScript, CSS/Sass, HTML, C#, Cypress, Jest, Redux, GraphQL, MongoDB

Frameworks & Libraries

→ React, NodeJs, TailwindCSS, .NET

Tools

→ Git, Heroku, Docker, Webpack, Vercel.